{
  "HtmlEasy": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is the purpose of the HTML <br> element?",
          "answer1": "To define a table row",
          "answer2": "To insert a line break",
          "answer3": "To create a numbered list",
          "correctAnswer": "To insert a line break"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
          "answer1": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
          "answer2": "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
          "answer3": "Home Tool Markup Language",
          "correctAnswer": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "Which HTML element is used for creating a hyperlink?",
          "answer1": "<a>",
          "answer2": "<link>",
          "answer3": "<hyperlink>",
          "correctAnswer": "<a>"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting an image?",
          "answer1": "<img>",
          "answer2": "<image>",
          "answer3": "<picture>",
          "correctAnswer": "<img>"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the purpose of the HTML <head> element?",
          "answer1": "To define the main content of the document",
          "answer2": "To define the header section of the document",
          "answer3": "To define the title of the document",
          "correctAnswer": "To define the header section of the document"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Which HTML element is used to define the largest heading?",
          "answer1": "<h6>",
          "answer2": "<h1>",
          "answer3": "<heading>",
          "correctAnswer": "<h1>"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a line break?",
          "answer1": "<linebreak>",
          "answer2": "<break>",
          "answer3": "<br>",
          "correctAnswer": "<br>"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Which HTML element is used to define a table?",
          "answer1": "<table>",
          "answer2": "<tab>",
          "answer3": "<tbl>",
          "correctAnswer": "<table>"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that opens in a new tab?",
          "answer1": "<a href='https://www.example.com' target='_blank'>Link</a>",
          "answer2": "<a href='https://www.example.com' new-tab>Link</a>",
          "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com' target='new'>Link</a>",
          "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com' target='_blank'>Link</a>"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "What is the correct HTML element for defining important text?",
          "answer1": "<i>",
          "answer2": "<b>",
          "answer3": "<strong>",
          "correctAnswer": "<strong>"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Which HTML element is used to define a level of importance for content?",
            "answer1": "<imp>",
            "answer2": "<importance>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<strong>"
          },
          {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "What does the HTML <canvas> element define?",
            "answer1": "A container for multimedia content",
            "answer2": "A container for graphics",
            "answer3": "A container for JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer": "A container for graphics"
          },
          {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a table header?",
            "answer1": "<head>",
            "answer2": "<tableheader>",
            "answer3": "<th>",
            "correctAnswer": "<th>"
          },
          {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
            "answer1": "<a src='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer2": "<a url='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a horizontal rule?",
            "answer1": "<line>",
            "answer2": "<hr>",
            "answer3": "<linebreak>",
            "correctAnswer": "<hr>"
          },
          {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a numeric input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='number'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='numeric'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='text' pattern='[0-9]'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='number'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a definition list?",
            "answer1": "<ol>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<dl>",
            "correctAnswer": "<dl>"
          },
          {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a text input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='textfield'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='text'>",
            "answer3": "<textfield>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='text'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a>email@example.com</a>",
            "answer2": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "answer3": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines the title of a work (e.g., a book, a song, or a movie)?",
            "answer1": "<headline>",
            "answer2": "<title>",
            "answer3": "<heading>",
            "correctAnswer": "<title>"
          },
          {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a radio button?",
            "answer1": "<input type='radio'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='button'>",
            "answer3": "<radio>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='radio'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines a section in a document?",
            "answer1": "<section>",
            "answer2": "<div>",
            "answer3": "<article>",
            "correctAnswer": "<section>"
          },
          {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 33,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 34,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 35,
            "question": "What does the HTML <canvas> element define?",
            "answer1": "A container for multimedia content",
            "answer2": "A container for graphics",
            "answer3": "A container for JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer": "A container for graphics"
          },
          {
            "id": 36,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a table header?",
            "answer1": "<head>",
            "answer2": "<tableheader>",
            "answer3": "<th>",
            "correctAnswer": "<th>"
          },
          {
            "id": 37,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
            "answer1": "<a src='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer2": "<a url='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 38,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a horizontal rule?",
            "answer1": "<line>",
            "answer2": "<hr>",
            "answer3": "<linebreak>",
            "correctAnswer": "<hr>"
          },
          {
            "id": 39,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a numeric input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='number'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='numeric'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='text' pattern='[0-9]'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='number'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a definition list?",
            "answer1": "<ol>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<dl>",
            "correctAnswer": "<dl>"
          },
          {
            "id": 41,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for defining important text?",
            "answer1": "<i>",
            "answer2": "<b>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<strong>"
          },
          {
            "id": 42,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a checkbox?",
            "answer1": "<checkbox>",
            "answer2": "<input type='check'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='checkbox'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='checkbox'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 43,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a level of importance for content?",
            "answer1": "<imp>",
            "answer2": "<importance>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<strong>"
          },
          {
            "id": 44,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 45,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 46,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 47,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "What does the HTML <canvas> element define?",
            "answer1": "A container for multimedia content",
            "answer2": "A container for graphics",
            "answer3": "A container for JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer": "A container for graphics"
          },
          {
            "id": 51,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a table header?",
            "answer1": "<head>",
            "answer2": "<tableheader>",
            "answer3": "<th>",
            "correctAnswer": "<th>"
          },
          {
            "id": 52,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
            "answer1": "<a src='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer2": "<a url='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 53,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a horizontal rule?",
            "answer1": "<line>",
            "answer2": "<hr>",
            "answer3": "<linebreak>",
            "correctAnswer": "<hr>"
          },
          {
            "id": 54,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a numeric input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='number'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='numeric'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='text' pattern='[0-9]'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='number'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 55,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a definition list?",
            "answer1": "<ol>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<dl>",
            "correctAnswer": "<dl>"
          },
          {
            "id": 56,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a text input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='textfield'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='text'>",
            "answer3": "<textfield>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='text'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 57,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a>email@example.com</a>",
            "answer2": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "answer3": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 58,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines the title of a work (e.g., a book, a song, or a movie)?",
            "answer1": "<headline>",
            "answer2": "<title>",
            "answer3": "<heading>",
            "correctAnswer": "<title>"
          },
          {
            "id": 59,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a radio button?",
            "answer1": "<input type='radio'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='button'>",
            "answer3": "<radio>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='radio'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 60,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines a section in a document?",
            "answer1": "<section>",
            "answer2": "<div>",
            "answer3": "<article>",
            "correctAnswer": "<section>"
          },
          {
            "id": 61,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 62,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 63,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 64,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 65,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 66,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 67,
            "question": "What does the HTML <canvas> element define?",
            "answer1": "A container for multimedia content",
            "answer2": "A container for graphics",
            "answer3": "A container for JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer": "A container for graphics"
          },
          {
            "id": 68,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a table header?",
            "answer1": "<head>",
            "answer2": "<tableheader>",
            "answer3": "<th>",
            "correctAnswer": "<th>"
          },
          {
            "id": 69,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
            "answer1": "<a src='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer2": "<a url='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 70,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a horizontal rule?",
            "answer1": "<line>",
            "answer2": "<hr>",
            "answer3": "<linebreak>",
            "correctAnswer": "<hr>"
          },
          {
            "id": 71,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a numeric input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='number'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='numeric'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='text' pattern='[0-9]'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='number'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 72,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a definition list?",
            "answer1": "<ol>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<dl>",
            "correctAnswer": "<dl>"
          },
          {
            "id": 73,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a text input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='textfield'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='text'>",
            "answer3": "<textfield>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='text'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 74,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a>email@example.com</a>",
            "answer2": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "answer3": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 75,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines the title of a work (e.g., a book, a song, or a movie)?",
            "answer1": "<headline>",
            "answer2": "<title>",
            "answer3": "<heading>",
            "correctAnswer": "<title>"
          },
          {
            "id": 76,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a radio button?",
            "answer1": "<input type='radio'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='button'>",
            "answer3": "<radio>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='radio'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 77,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines a section in a document?",
            "answer1": "<section>",
            "answer2": "<div>",
            "answer3": "<article>",
            "correctAnswer": "<section>"
          },
          {
            "id": 78,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 79,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 80,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 81,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 82,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 83,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 84,
            "question": "What does the HTML <canvas> element define?",
            "answer1": "A container for multimedia content",
            "answer2": "A container for graphics",
            "answer3": "A container for JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer": "A container for graphics"
          },
          {
            "id": 85,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a table header?",
            "answer1": "<head>",
            "answer2": "<tableheader>",
            "answer3": "<th>",
            "correctAnswer": "<th>"
          },
          {
            "id": 86,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
            "answer1": "<a src='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer2": "<a url='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "answer3": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='https://www.example.com'>Link</a>"
          },
          {
            "id": 87,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a horizontal rule?",
            "answer1": "<line>",
            "answer2": "<hr>",
            "answer3": "<linebreak>",
            "correctAnswer": "<hr>"
          },
          {
            "id": 88,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a numeric input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='number'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='numeric'>",
            "answer3": "<input type='text' pattern='[0-9]'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='number'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 89,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a definition list?",
            "answer1": "<ol>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<dl>",
            "correctAnswer": "<dl>"
          },
          {
            "id": 90,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a text input field?",
            "answer1": "<input type='textfield'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='text'>",
            "answer3": "<textfield>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='text'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 91,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a>email@example.com</a>",
            "answer2": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "answer3": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='email' value='email@example.com'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 92,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines the title of a work (e.g., a book, a song, or a movie)?",
            "answer1": "<headline>",
            "answer2": "<title>",
            "answer3": "<heading>",
            "correctAnswer": "<title>"
          },
          {
            "id": 93,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for creating a radio button?",
            "answer1": "<input type='radio'>",
            "answer2": "<input type='button'>",
            "answer3": "<radio>",
            "correctAnswer": "<input type='radio'>"
          },
          {
            "id": 94,
            "question": "Which HTML element defines a section in a document?",
            "answer1": "<section>",
            "answer2": "<div>",
            "answer3": "<article>",
            "correctAnswer": "<section>"
          },
          {
            "id": 95,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a video?",
            "answer1": "<media>",
            "answer2": "<video>",
            "answer3": "<movie>",
            "correctAnswer": "<video>"
          },
          {
            "id": 96,
            "question": "In HTML, which tag is used to define a list item?",
            "answer1": "<li>",
            "answer2": "<ul>",
            "answer3": "<ol>",
            "correctAnswer": "<li>"
          },
          {
            "id": 97,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
            "answer1": "<em>",
            "answer2": "<italic>",
            "answer3": "<strong>",
            "correctAnswer": "<em>"
          },
          {
            "id": 98,
            "question": "Which HTML attribute specifies the width of an image?",
            "answer1": "width",
            "answer2": "size",
            "answer3": "height",
            "correctAnswer": "width"
          },
          {
            "id": 99,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
            "answer1": "<linebreak>",
            "answer2": "<br>",
            "answer3": "<lb>",
            "correctAnswer": "<br>"
          },
          {
            "id": 100,
            "question": "What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink that links to an email address?",
            "answer1": "<a href='email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer2": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>",
            "answer3": "<mail>email@example.com</mail>",
            "correctAnswer": "<a href='mailto:email@example.com'>Email me</a>"
          }
      ]
      
}